

PROFILE

Music production engineer, musician and electrician.

I have participated in international tours and contributed to audio projects in sound design, composition, recording and music production.

I also have experience in auditoriums, sports events, conferences, musicals, among others, participating in different areas from planning to the execution and monitoring of the events.

KEY FEATURES

Nacionality: Mexican

Age: 23

University: **ITESM**

Music Production Career:

Engineering

Spanish & English Languages:

TOEFL: 550

CEFR: **B1**

CONTACT

6ta de Felipe Carrillo Puerto, #514, Ricardo Flores Magón, Atlixco, Puebla, México.

+(52) 2441069527

fcojavier2711@gmail.com

/javier.sax.flores

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Musician

Orquesta de Cámara de Atlixco (January 2014 - August 2019)

ITESM: Chamber Assembly and Musical Theatre (August 2014 - December 2019)

Compañía Folklórica Magisterial de Hidalgo (April 2018 - Today)

Yilan International Childen's Folklore and Folkgame Festival, Taiwán (July & August 2018)

Sharjah Heritage Days Festival, United Arab Emirates. (April 2019)

Electrician

Econodiesel de Atlixco. (2013 - December 2017)

Hardware Development

AIRA Studio (May to July 2019)

Events Logistics & Sound Engineer

Orquesta Gran Ensamble (August 2017 to December 2017):

Placement of microphones for concerts and monitor mixing engineer.

La casa de la música de Viena en Puebla (January to July 2018):

Audio technician in charge of microphone setting and front of house audio mixing for the auditorium.

Universidad de las Américas Puebla (June 2019-Today):

Audio Engineer and light technician in charge of medium size auditorium made for 600 people, a small movie teathre, a conference hall and outdoor venues.

Audio set up and operation for diferent events like: conferences, musicals, opera & concerts.

Audio equipment and facilities management and maintenance.

EDUCATION

2011 CBTIS 16

Electric Technician

2013 CCU BUAP ARTS SCHOOL

Musical Formation

2014 ITESM

Music Production Engineer

2018 The College of Central Europe

"Managing in the Creative Economy"

Winter certificate in Brno, Czech Republic.

TECHNICAL TOOLS

DIGITAL AUDIO MIXERS

Behringer, A&H, Roland, Yamaha & Avid.

ANALOG AUDIO MIXERS

API, Mackie & Yamaha.

LIGHTING CONSOLES

ETC Element.

OTHER TOOLS Digital and analog signal processors DMX and Dimmeable stage lights Microphone techniques Audio amplifiers Video tools

AoIP & Dante networking

REAS OF EXPERIENCE

- Live audio
- Audio recording
- Audio mixing
- Audio systems calibration
- **Events Logistics**
- Stage Lighting
- Audio maintenance
- Administration
- **Electrical Design**

PERSONAL SKILLS

- Leadership
- Team working
- Hard working
- Fast learning
- **Customer Support**
- Creativity
- Artistic sense
- Technical Knowledge
- Troubleshooting
- Attention to detail

Sibelius **Protools** HTML5 **Plugins** JAVA



Windows OS Mac OS Ubuntu OS

